# Patryk Mazur



## **Personal Info**

**Email** 

mazurpatryk9@gmail.com

**Phone** 

+48 531885798

## **Skills**

Conscientiousness

Punctuality

Accuracy

Kindness

**Good Appearance** 

## Languages

Spanish - A1

Polish - C2

English - B1

Completion of an English language certificate at B1 level

# Hobby/Interest

Computer graphics Foreign cuisine Travel Crime novels

Technology news

I am a final year student of Technical and Information Technology Education at the Lublin University of Technology. I have done a total of 2 months work experience in Portugal on the Erasmus+ programme. I am fluent in English. I am kind, conscientious and accurate.

## **Work History**

2020-10 Member of the Animgraf student club - present

2022-09 Teacher of Technology/Informatics

- 2022-09 Primary School No. 3, Dęblin

Professional practice

· Teaching technology and information technology classes

2019-07 **Receptionist** 

- 2019-07 Pensjonat Kazimierski, Kazimierz Dolny

Job placement

- Managing bookings and receiving payments
- Data entry into the online system

2019-06 **Waiter** 

- 2019-06 Grande Hotel da Póvoa, Póvoa do Varzim

Apprenticeship

2018-08 Receptionist

- 2018-08 Hotel Pikul, Puławy

Job placement

- Managing bookings and taking payments
- Caring for the appearance of the reception and the image of the establishment
- Performing minor translations (Polish into English)

2018-05 **Waiter** 

- 2018-05 Estalagem Santo André, Póvoa de Varzim

**Apprenticeships** 

- · Professional service to restaurant and hotel guests
- Cooperation with kitchen staff and other teams

### **Education**

2020-10 technical and computer education, engineer - present

Lublin University of Technology, Lublin

2016-09 **Hospitality, Hotel technician** 

- 2020-04 Vocational School Complex No. 2, Dęblin

### **Certificates**

**Driving licence category B** 

**Certificate from the "Orange Goes Green" workshop**